This zip file contains graphics for every tileset within the game VVVVVV, excluding the Tower because that tileset has
about 30 different palettes plus a background, so no.

The "tiles" folder contains the Space Station stuff (ExGFX86), and the "tiles2" folder contains everything else
(ExGFX85), as that is how the graphics are set up in the actual game files. There's also a bin file for animations
(ExGFX87), which include conveyors  (use your own custom blocks for those), the Warp Zone background, and the
animated tiles in the endgame sequence.

Note that the Space Station map16 and the map16 for everything else both use FG3, so you'll have to do some tweaking
if you want them both in the same sublevel. You'll also need to do some tweaking to use more than one tile palette
in the same sublevel, and that's why there are alllll those different palette files.

Also, only the Warp Zone sample level contains animations for the WZ background. However, the other animations are in all
sample levels.

It's up to you to get custom blocks for the conveyors and one-way tiles, because I don't think I'm supposed to do that.

  ████████████████
████████████████████
██████    ████    ██
██████    ████    ██
████████████████████
████████████████████
██████            ██
████████        ████
  ████████████████
      ████████
  ████████████████
████████████████████
████████████████████
████████████████████
████  ████████  ████
████  ████████  ████
    ████████████
    ████    ████
  ██████    ██████
  ██████    ██████
  ██████    ██████